A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness House drawings, SG 2 FA247
Rockefeller Archive Center
- First Floor, 1907-1983; 3
  - Building/Floor Plans, 3.1
    - Reception Room
      - 2/5/1908, 328 NY 33 (Folder 52)
        South Elevation of Reception Room, # 1-26 3/8"x18 3/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-26 5/8'x18 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 329 NY 33 (Folder 53)
        East Elevation, Reception Room, # 1-2 Pieces of Paper Glued Together (Left edge), 30 5/8"x17 3/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-31 "x17 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 330 NY 33 (Folder 53)
        North Elevation, Reception Room, # 1-25 2/8"x17 3/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-25"x17 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, # 3-25 5/8"x17 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - undated, 360/6153 (Folder 53)
        Plan Showing Finish Plaster Lines, Reception Room, Written on the Back in Pencil, Own Bed Rm, Reception Room, 23 3/8"x18", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A, (D.S. Hess and Co.)
        Received 4/10/1908 Charles T. Wills
      - undated, 360/6153A (Folder 54)
        Elevation Showing Grounds, etc, North Elevation, Reception Room, Section on Mantel 21"x14 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A, (D.S. Hess and Co.)
      - undated, 360/6153B (Folder 54)
        Elevation Showing Grounds, etc, South Elevation, Reception Room, 17 1/2"x14 5/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, D.S. Hess and Co.
      - undated, 360/6153C (Folder 54)
        Elevation Showing Grounds, etc, East Elevation, Reception Room, 23 1/2"x14 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A, (D.S. Hess and Co.)
      - undated, 360/6153C (Folder 54)
        South Elevation of Reception Room, 23 1/4"x21", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, D.S. Hess and Co.
      - undated, 360/6153D (Folder 55)
        Elevation Showing Grounds, etc, West Elevation, Reception Room, Written on the Back in Pencil-Hess-Drawings of Reception Room 1st Floor, 21 1/8"x14 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A, (D.S. Hess and Co.)
      - undated, 360/6153F (Folder 55)
        North Elevation of Reception Room, 23"x21", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, D.S. Hess and Co.
      - undated, 360/6153H (Folder 55)
        East Elevation of Reception Room, 32 5/8"x21 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, D.S. Hess and Co.
      - undated, 360/6153I (Folder 55)
        West Elevation of Reception Room, 32"x21 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, D.S. Hess and Co.
      - 1981 May 1, 948 (Office Copy), 360/6153Q (Folder 56)
        Change to Panels in Wainscot to Accommodate Register Faces, Reception Room, Written on the Front in Pencil, Revised 1" Scale Wainscot Panels RR, Written on the Back in Pencil, Reception Room Panels, 21 3/4"x12 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, D.S. Hess and Co.
        Received 5/26/1908 Hale and Rogers
      - 5/8/1908, 953 (Office Copy), Drawing Number 42 (Folder 56)
        Plan of Base in Reception Room, Full Size Section of Base, 21 7/8"x20 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
      - undated, 1092 (Office Copy) (Folder 56)
        Elevation Showing Reception Room, Side of Sliding Door Toward Hall, 8 1/4"x13", Tracing Paper, Architects, D.S. Hess and Co.
        Received 7/18/1908 Hale and Rogers
      - undated (2/5/1908), No Number Listed (Rolled with 330 NY 33) (Folder 56)
        Cases in Reception Room, Harkness Residence, Harkness Residence Allocations, (Image of a Butler Drawn for Scale), 15 3/8"x18", Tracing Paper, Architects, J.G. Rogers of Hale and Rogers
      - undated (2/5/1908), No Number Listed (Rolled with 330 NY 33) (Folder 56)
        Cases in Reception Room, Harkness Residence, File Harkness Residence Allocations 15 1/4"x18", Tracing Paper, Architects, J.G. Rogers of Hale and Rogers
      - undated (2/5/1908), No Number Listed (Rolled with 330 NY 33) (Folder 56)
        Cases in Reception Room, Harkness Residence, (Image of a Butler (left side) and measurements are in the drawing), 15 1/4"x18", Tracing Paper, Architects, J.G. Rogers of Hale and Rogers
      - undated (2/5/1908), No Number Listed (Rolled with 330 NY 33) (Folder 56)
        Cases in Reception Room, Harkness Residence, File Harkness Residence Allocations, Image of Butler Drawn for Scale (right side) 14 1/4"x16 7/8", Tracing Paper, Architects, J.G. Rogers of Hale and Rogers
    - Ladies' Dressing Room
      - 2/5/1908, 331 NY 33 (Folder 57)
        Ladies Dressing Room, Plan, North Elevation of Dressing Room and Toilet, East Elevation of Toilet, West Elevation, South Elevation and East Elevation, General Notes on the Right Side, (2 Copies) # 1-33 7/8"x24 1/2", Tracing Paper, # 2-34 1/4"x24 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 7/18/1908, 1096 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 75 (Folder 57)
        Plan of Toilet Off Ladies Dressing Room First Floor, Section Thro' Base and Floor, A piece of tracing paper had been glued to the drawing to show detail, Written on the Back in Pencil, Ladies Toilet 1st Fl, 17 3/4"x13", Diazo Blue Print, Tracing Paper-8 3/4"x6", Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
    - Vestibule and Entrance Hall
      - 4/29/1907, 301 NY 33 (Folder 58)
        Sketches of Entrance Hall-Looking North, Looking East, Looking South, Detail of Entrance Hall, Entrance Hall Ceiling, Vestibule-Looking South, Looking North, Sketches of Stair Hall, First Story-Looking North, Looking East, Ceiling Plan, # 1-42 1/4"x20 1/8", Linen, # 2-42"x20", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 1/22/1908, 321 NY 33 (Folder 59)
        Details Showing Marble work in Entrance Vestibule, North Elevation of Vestibule, South Elevation of Vestibule-Same for West Elevation, East Elevation, Detail Plan of Floor, # 1-32 1/2"x29 1/2", Linen, # 2- 32 5/8"x29 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 322 NY 33 (Folder 60)
        Plan, Entrance Hall, # 1-30 3/8"x24 1/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-30 1/4"x24 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 323 NY33 (#1-No Number-Torn Off) (Folder 58)
        Entrance Hall, North Elevation, East Elevation, General Notes on Right Side, # 1-44"x18" Tracing Paper, # 2-44 1/4"x18", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 324 NY33 (Folder 59)
        Entrance Hall, South Elevation, West Elevation, # 1-44"x18", Tracing Paper, # 2-44"x18", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 325 NY 33 (Folder 60)
        Entrance Hall, Ceiling Developed Low Relief Plaster, # 1-28 1/2"x23 7/8", Tracing Paper, # 2-28 1/4"x23 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - undated, 601 (Office Copy) Drawing Number 1 (Folder 61)
        Scale Layout of Marble Ceiling Work in Vestibule, Reflected Plan of Ceiling, Elevation Looking North, Elevation Looking East, Elevation Looking South {Main Entrance Door}, Elevation Looking West {Vestibule Door to Main Hall}, 24 1/8"x22", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
        Received 6/30/19220? James Gamble Rogers
      - 3/25/1908, 780 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 13 (Folder 61)
        Plan Showing Flooring in Vestibule, First Floor, 20 1/2"x14, Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
      - 5/28/1908, 973 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing 6A (Folder 61)
        Full Scale Detail of Cornice in Vestibule Showing Drops, Plan of Soffit, Section A-A, 17 1/2"x17", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
      - 6/15/1908, 1004 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 54 Second Copy Doesn't Have an Office Copy # (Folder 61)
        Plan of Marble Base in Entrance Hall, # 1-26 1/4"x18 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitel's Detail of Marble Base in Entrance Hall, First Floor, 26 1/8"x18 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
      - 3/3/1908-6/10/1908, Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 4 (Folder 62)
        Plan and Elevation of Vestibule First Floor, # 1-Written on the Back in Pencil, Drawing No. 4, Traitel Marble Co, Plan and Elevation Vestibule 1st Floor, 36 1/4"x30 1/2" (Octagonal Shape), Diazo Blue Print, # 2-Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitel's Detail of Vestibule First Floor, 36 3/8"x30 5/8" (Octagonal Shape), Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
        3/3/1908 #1-Revised 3/10/1908 #2-Revised 6/10/1908
    - Front Door
      - 6/29/1942, Drawing No. 2 (Folder 63)
        One Set of Screens as Shown For Entrance, First Floor, Plan Section A, Section B, Written on the Back in Pen, Screen, Main Entrance Door, 6/42, 16 5/8"x15 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, William Somerville, Inc,
      - 4/28/1909, 205 NY 33 (Folder 63)
        Storm Door for Main Entrance, Note on Left Side, 15 1/4"x14", Tracing Paper, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/21 (No Year Available), 1023 (the number was partially ripped but 1023 was written on the back) (Folder 63)
        Pro...Ire..Grill, and Servants Gate, Size N/A (in several pieces), Diazo Blue Print, Separate Piece of Paper Attached, Jno Wms Bronze Fndy and Iron Wks-, Is. Dwg. Bronze Grill w/-Servants' Gate, 1023 (Handwritten in Pencil), 5"x3", Paper, Architects, Jno Williams, Inc., Bronze Foundry and Iron Works
      - undated, 1200 (Office Copy) (Folder 63)
        A Suggestion for Fastening the Storm Door to the Bronze Grill, 23 1/4"x17 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, N/A
        Received 5/14/1909 Hale and Rogers
      - 9/1925, Sheet A1 (Folder 63)
        New Portable White Pine Enclosures for Main Entrance to Residence, Scale Elevation, Section and Full Scale Details, 24 1/4"x15", Tracing Paper, Architects, The Davis-Speyer Co., Architectural Woodwork
        Received 9/25/1925 Jas Gamble Rogers
    - Stair Hall
      - 12/20/1907, 316 NY 33 (Folder 64)
        Bronze Rail and Ramp, #1-16 5/8"x20", Tracing Paper, # 2-19 1/4"x23 7/8", Polyester Paper, # 3-19 1/4"x23 7/8", Polyester Paper, # 4-19 1/8"x23 3/4", Polyester Paper, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 1/21/1908, 319 NY 33 -# 2-No Number (Folder 65)
        Scale Drawings of Marble Work on Main Staircase, Section Looking South, Section Looking West, # 1-36"x53 1/2", Linen, # 2- (in 2 Pieces) 35 1/2"x54" and 5 1/4"x6", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 1/21/1908, 320 NY 33 #2- No Number (Folder 65)
        Scale Drawings of Marble Work on Main Staircase, Section Looking North, Section Looking East, # 1-36"x53 1/2", Linen, # 2- (in two pieces) 30 1/4"x@ 46" and @ 5 1/4"x45", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Haleand Rogers
      - 1981 May 29, 333 NY 33 (Folder 66)
        Plan of Stair Hall, Elevation of Register (Looking East), # 1-32 7/8"x20 1/2", Tracing Paper, # 2-33 3/8"x20 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 334 NY 33 (Folder 66)
        North Elevation of Stair Hall, General Notes on the Right Side, # 1-33 1/4"x20 1/2", Tracing Paper, # 2-33 5/8"x20 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 335 NY 33 (Folder 67)
        East Elevation, West Elevation of Stair Hall, # 1-33"x20 1/2", Tracing Paper, # 2-33 5/8"x20 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 336 NY 33 (Folder 67)
        South Elevation of Stair Hall, # 1-20 1/2"x32", Tracing Paper, # 2-33 5/8"x20 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 4/10/1908, 399-1 NY 33 (Folder 67)
        Plan of Ceiling Light Over Main Stairs, Sec "A-A", Sec "C-C", Bottom of "I" Beam, # 1-24 3/4"x15", Tracing Paper, # 2-24 1/2"x15 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 5/23/1908, 399-6 NY 33 (Folder 68)
        Supplementary Plan of Ceiling and Ceiling Light Over Main Staircase, # 1-25 1/8"x15 5/8", Tracing Paper, # 2-25"x15 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - undated, 931 (Office Copy) T1 (Folder 68)
        Stair First Floor to Second Platform, Written on the Back in Pencil, Staircase, 18 7/8"x12 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
        Received 6/10/1908 Charles T. Wills
      - undated, 716 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 7 (Folder 68)
        No Title, Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitels Drawings No. 7, Plan and Elevation of Stair Hall, First Floor, {Shape is Octagonal} 47 1/4"x29" (A Portion of the Right Edge is Detached) 5 1/2"x17 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
      - undated, 745 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 9 (Folder 65)
        Plan and Elevation of Entrance Hall, Section on Line A-A, Section on Line C-C, Section on Line D-D, Written on the Back in Pencil, Entrance Hall, Marble Work, 40 5/8"x41 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
        Received 3/24/1908 Charles T. Wills, 3/25/1908 Hale and Rogers
      - 3/26/1908, 781 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 14 (Folder 68)
        Plan of Marble Floor in Stair Hall, First Floor, 24 1/8"x15 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
      - undated, 1072 (Office Copy) (Folder 68)
        First Floor Landing to Stairs, 20 3/8"x16", Tracing Paper, Architects, N/A (Probably Hale and Rogers)
        Received 7/11/1908 Hale and Rogers
      - undated, 1073 (Office Copy) (Folder 68)
        Plan of the First Story, 20 1/2"x16", Tracing Paper, Architects, N/A (Probably Hale and Rogers)
      - 4/15/1908, Revised 4/27/1908; Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 27 (Folder 69)
        Developed Elevation of Asher on Walls, Main Stairs First to Second Floor, Written on the Back in Pencil, Traitel's Drawing-No. 27-Developed Elevation of Asher on Wall, Main Stairs From First to Second Floors, #1-43"x20 1/2", # 2-7/8"x9 7/8", # 3-9 1/8"x18" (Longest Point), Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
    - Elevator Vestibule
      - 5/12/1908, P-64, 914 (Folder 70)
        Elevator Vestibule, First Story, Plan, North and West Elevation, 23 1/4"x33 1/2", Paper, Architects, Pottier and Stymus Co.
    - Men's Dressing Room
      - 2/5/1908, 332 NY 33 (Folder 71)
        Men's Dressing Room, Plan, North Elevation, South Elevation, East Elevation, West Elevation, Door to W.C., # 1-2 Pieces of Paper Glued Together on the Left Edge, 37 1/2"x26 7/8", Tracing Paper, # 2-38"x26 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 7/7/1908, 1062 (Office Copy), Drawing Number 68 (Folder 71)
        Plan and Elevations of Men's Dressing Room First Floor, North and West Elevation, South Elevation, East Elevation, 25 5/8"x26 1/2, Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
    - Butler's Pantry
      - undated, 0-4 (Folder 72)
        Special Butler's Pantry Refrigerator, Elevation, Plan, Section, Written on the Back in Pencil, Refrigerator Drawings and Dubois MF'G Co's Drawing of Refrigerators, 26 1/4"x19 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Dubois Manufacturing Co.
      - 2/6/1908, 342 NY 33 (Folder 73)
        Butler's Pantry Details, Plan of Butler's Pantry, North Side, West Side, and South Side of Butler's Pantry, # 1-45 1/8"x28", Linen, # 2-45 1/4"x27 3/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - undated, 993 (Office Copy) (Folder 72)
        Special Butler's Pantry Refrigerator, Plan, Elevation, Section, Written on the Back in Pencil, Kitchens and Pantry, 26 3/8"x19 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Dubois Manufacturing Co.
      - 1981 July 24, P-33, 791 (Folder 72)
        Butler's Pantry, First Story, 19"x20", Paper, Architects, N/A, (Probably Pottier and Stymus Co.)
      - undated, P-34, (700 Number is torn off) (Folder 72)
        West and East Side of Butler's Pantry, Writing on the Back in Pencil but It Is Cut Off, 24 1/4"x19 3/4", Paper, Architects, Pottier and Stymus Co.
      - undated, P-35, 789 (Folder 72)
        South, Side of Butler's Pantry, First Floor, 18 1/8"x21", Paper, Architects, Pottier and Stymus Co.
      - 4/13/1908, P-36, 788 (Folder 72)
        North, Side of the Butler's Pantry, First Floor, 18"x20 1/2", Paper, Architects, Pottier and Stymus Co.
    - Dining Room
      - 4/25/1907, 302 NY 33 (Folder 74)
        Dining Room-North Elevation, East Elevation, and West Elevation, Dining Room Ceiling, Reception Room-East Elevation, South Elevation, and North Elevation, # 1-42 1/4"x20", Linen, # 2-42"x20", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 337 NY 33 (Folder 75)
        Dining Room, Plan, Half of the Floor, Half of the Ceiling, Note on the Right Side #1-32"x27 1/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-32 1/2"x27 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 338 NY 33 (Folder 75)
        Dining Room, East Elevation, # 1-38 3/8"x17 1/4", Tracing Paper, # 2-28 3/8"x17 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 339 NY 33 (Folder 75)
        South Elevation of Dining Room, # 1-28"x17 3/8", Tracing Paper, # 2-28"x17 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 340 NY 33 (Folder 76)
        Dining Room, West Elevation, General Notes on the Right Side, # 1-27 1/4"x17", Tracing Paper, # 2-28"x17, Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 341 NY 33 (Folder 76)
        Dining Room, North Elevation, # 1-28 1/8"x17 1/2", Tracing Paper, # 2-28"x17 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 3/28/1908, 782 (Office Copy), Order Number 2627, Drawing Number 15 (Folder 76)
        Plan and Elevation of Dining Room, 31 1/4"x@ 27 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, The Traitel Marble Co.
      - undated, No Number Listed (Torn off) (Folder 77)
        Dining Room Ceiling, 37 1/4"x37 7/8", Paper, Architects, N/A (Torn)
        Received 6/5/1908 Hale and Rogers
    - Dining Room Vault and Safe
      - undated, 1907 (Folder 78)
        Silver Vault, Written on the Back in Pencil, Silver Vault, Hall Safe, Co's Detail, 20 1/4"x18 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hall's Safe Co.
  - HVAC, 3.2
    - 10/5/1982, AC-1, Job Number 26-82 (Folder 79)
      Proposed Air Conditioning System, First Floor, Plot Plan, Side Yard, 36 1/2"x20", Sepia Tone, Architects, P and O Air Control Co., Inc.
    - 5/24/1983, M-3 (Folder 80)
      Alterations to HVAC System, First Floor Plan and Second Floor Plan-HVAC and Electric, 49 1/4"x30 1/4", Paper, Architects, Stramandinoli, Mellusi and Khlyavich
    - 4/9/1907, No Number Listed (Folder 79)
      First Story Plan, Notes on the Bottom, It's a Copy, Paper Size-24"x18 1/4", Image Size-23 1/4"x12 1/2", Paper, Architects, N/A
  - Plumbing, 3.3
    - 4/15/1907, 1366 (Folder 81)
      Plumbing Plans, First Story Plan, # 1-36 1/2"x18 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-It's a Copy, Paper Size-24"x18 1/4", Image Size-20 1/2"x10 1/4", Architects, Albert L. Webster, Civil and Sanitary Engineer
  - Electrical, 3.4
    - 12/28/1950-2/2/1953, Job Number 421, Drawing Number 2 (Folder 82-83)
      #2-Received 2/3/1953 Rogers and Butler #3-Received 7/3/1951 Rogers and Butler #6-Received 7/3/1951 Rogers and Butler
      Alteration to One East 75th St N.Y.C. for the Commonwealth Fund, First Floor Plan and Second Floor Plan, Mezzanine, Note on the Right Side, # 1-Written on the Back in Pen, Telephone, 1/25/1951-Exit Doors Revised, 4/10/1951-General Owner Requests-DV Removed, 4/23/1951-Plumbing and General Notes Added, 5/16/1951-Owner Requests, 5/22/1951-Drink Fountain Added-Near Rm 2-2, Removal Note Omitted-Rm 2-3, 42 1/4"x26 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, A Separate Sheet of Paper was Attached on the Top Right Corner: Diagram Made by Telephone Installer When Intercom Units # 33 and # 32 were Installed-6/1963, 13"x8", Paper, # 2-Electrical (Stamped), Revisions: 6/26/1951-First Floor-Clock Added in Space No. 1-3, New Picture Lights in Space No. 1-8, Second Floor-Outlets Omitted in Space No. 2-1 and 2-3, 2/2/1953-42 1/8"x26", Paper, # 3-Has the Architects Pencil Notations, 41 7/8"x26 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 4-No Electrical Stamp, 41 1/2"x26 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, # 5-Electrical (Stamped), 42"x26", Diazo Blue Print, # 6-Electrical (Stamped), 42"x26 1/2", Diazo Blue Print, # 7-Electrical, Revisions: 6/26/1951-First Floor-Clock Added in Space No. 1-3, New Picture Lights in Space No. 1-8, Second Floor-Outlets Omitted in Space No. 2-1 and 2-3, 2/2/1953-Revised as per Contractors Marked Up Drawings, 43 7/8"x28", Linen (Blue), # 8-First Floor Plan, Revised 12/5/1951: Exit Doors Revised, 41 7/8"x26", Paper, Architects # 1-Rogers and Butler, # 2-Rogers and Butler, Clifton E. Smith and Edward B. Silverman, Consulting Electrical Engineers, # 3-4-Rogers and Butler, # 5-7-Rogers and Butler, Clifton E. Smith and Edward B. Silverman, Consulting Electrical Engineers.
      #1-12/28/1950 #2-Revised 6/26/1951 #3-Revised 6/26/1951 #4-Revised 1/25/1951, 4/10/1951 #5-Revised 6/26/1951, 2/2/1953 Rogers & Butler #6-Revised 6/26/1951 #7-Revised 6/26/1951, 2/2/1953 #8-Revised 1/25/1951
    - undated, 1194 (Office Copy) (A69) (Folder 84)
      Full Size Detail of Dining Room Vault Reflector, 12"x17 7/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Lord Electric Company
      Received 10/20/1908 by Charles T. Wills and Hale and Rogers.
    - 4/14/1908-6/16/01908, Order Number 2047, 1824/2 (Folder 84)
      Panel -A- 1st Floor, Sheet Iron Box, Panels Aa and Ab 1st Floor, Iron Lined Wood Box, # 1-Written on the Back in Pencil, Panel Boards, Lord-Elec-Co's Drawings, 27"x18", Diazo Blue Print, # 2-26 3/4"x19", Diazo Blue Print, # 3-25 3/4"x20 3/8", Diazo Blue Print, # 4-Panel A, Aa, Ab 1st Floor, Sheet Iron Box, Written on the Back in Pencil, Panel Box 1 Floor, 13 1/4"x24 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, H. Krantz Manufacturing Co.
      #1-4/14/1908 #2-4/14/1908 #3-4/14/1908, Revised 5/2/1908 #4-6/16/01908
- Second Floor/Mezzanine, 1906-1982; 4
  - Building/Floor Plans, 4.1
    - 11/8/1906, 3 NY 33 (Folder 85)
      Second Floor Plan, 42"x21 7/8", Linen, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - 4/29/1907, 110 NY 33 (Folder 85)
      Second Floor, Mezzanine Floor (Between Second and Third Floors), and Third Floor Framing Plan, Section Through Fireplace in Library, in Reception Room, in Hall, Music Room, Dining Room, Section Through Framing at Floor Registers in Library, Section "B-B", Schedule of Grinder Sections, # 1-42"x32 1/4", Linen, # 2-42"x32", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - 4/29/1907, 303 NY 33 (Folder 85)
      Library-Ceiling, Library-North Elevation, West Elevation, East Elevation, Music Room-Ceiling, Music Room-East Elevation, West Elevation, North Elevation, Second Story Hall-South Elevation, North Elevation, # 1-42"x20 1/8", Linen, # 2-41"x20 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
    - Library
      - 11/12/1907, 310 NY 33 (Folder 86)
        Revised Details of Library Fireplace with Plans Through Enlarged Flue in Upper Stories, Section Through Protector at Back of Marble Lintel, Section, Section Through Inclined Sheet Iron Throat, Plan Through Chimney, Plan in Fifth Story, Plan in Fourth Story, Passage, Plan in Third Story, Plan in Second Story, 25 1/4"x17 7/8", Linen, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 346 NY 33 (Folder 86)
        Plan of Library, Half Plan of Floor, Half Plan of Ceiling, # 1-33 3/4"x28 1/8", Tracing Paper, # 2-33 7/8"x21 1/4", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 347 NY 33 (Folder 86)
        Library West Elevation, Note on the Right Side, # 1-33 1/4"x17", Tracing Paper, # 2-33 1/2"x17 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 348 NY 33 (Folder 87)
        Library South Elevation, # 1-33 5/8"x17", Tracing Paper, # 2-33 3/4"x17", Diazo Blue Print. Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 349 NY 33 (Folder 87)
        Library East Elevation, # 1-32 1/4"x17", Tracing Paper, # 2-33 5/8"x17 1/8", Diazo Blue Print, Architects, Hale and Rogers
      - 2/5/1908, 350 NY 33 (Folder 87)